question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "English new wave musician Gary Numan founded the video game development company Facepunch Studios in March 2009.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In the Super Mario series, the character Pauline is a Princess like Princess Peach.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In the Mortal Kombat series the &quot;Deadly Alliance&quot; consists of Shang Tsung and Quan Chi",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In Resident Evil 4, the Chicago Typewriter has infinite ammo.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Pac-Man was invented by the designer Toru Iwatani while he was eating pizza.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In Team Fortress 2, the weapon &quot;Your Eternal Reward&quot; is a reference to the 1992 film Aladdin.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Gordon Freeman, the protagonist of &quot;Half-Life&quot;, is said to have once had a ponytail.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Rollercoaster Tycoon 1 and 2 were developed by Chris Sawyer.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "&quot;Half-Life 2&quot; runs on the Source Engine.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Doki Doki Literature Club was developed in Japan.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
    ]
